Move!
My son!
My son, my son!
I'm sorry.
Trying to catch a thief.
My name is Li Hongqi.
I'm a policeman.
Move!
I'm chasing a thief
three thousand kilometers from my jurisdiction
all because of a call from my mother-in-law.
Mediation is over!
It only makes things messier!
It doesn't matter how many of you are here.
"A shameless freeloader" is what you called me!
I will never forget it.
- Excuse me.  - You don't have anything, right?
- It's no use.  - All the neighbors have complained about you.
So we will die together.
I can't calm down！
Get out, everyone!
Out!
Take it easy.
Put the knife down.
Can't.
Shoot me, why not!
Calm down.
Bring Li Hongqi.
We can talk about this.
Don't get carried away.
No, go ahead.
Until death do us part, right?
What are you doing?
My...
my mother-in-law
He is waving a knife.
Hurry up.
I'm not well.
Forward.
You all call me a loser.
I'll show you everything
what am I made of!
Listen to me.
- Give me a second, aunt.  - Can I take your place?
Get lost!
If you take one more step...
Excuse me.
my phone,
my phone.
Go ahead, aunt.
Let's get it out.
Calm, calm.
Two.
Three.
Ouch.
Sure, sure.
When?
- You're killing me.  - Yes, absolutely.
Let's do it.
I'm stuck in the neck!
Bye,
I need to take a few days off.
A few days off?
It's the first time in three and a half years.
What is celebrated?
Taozi's biological mother called.
He said that I have to give Taozi
a proper wedding,
and she will help me
in Haijiao.
As?
Are you already on the plane?
Yes.
It's an emergency case.
The local police don't give me any respite.
Where are you going?
Haijiao.
Haijiao?
You have been married for two years,
and just have the wedding now?
Ridiculous.
What can I do then?
His mother wants to keep it a secret,
He wants me to surprise his daughter.
Her parents divorced when she was little.
I haven't even met the mother.
I'll go visit your mother when I have time.
You have a job to do.
There is no need to see it.
Foolishness.
Since I'll be there anyway,
We could spend some time together.
It is a real piece.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
What if
Taozi doesn't want to do it?
Not that this is a case
which you can jump to.
I imagine,
I'll go to my mother-in-law first.
When everything is ready,
I'll talk to Taozi.
What if you can't convince Taozi?
If I can't convince Taozi,
I'll talk to his mother.
You're not thinking it through.
Following.
Recipe, please.
Take care of yourself,
do you hear me?
Don't worry.
I have to go.
Police?
Criminal or community?
Criminal.
Are you going to Haijiao for a case?
For my wedding.
Second marriage?
How can you know?
You know, the second time
It's not bad at all.
Don't be so sure.
It's my first marriage.
My fault, don't be angry.
My name is Xinxin.
What is yours?
Li Hongqi.
Hongqi, like a red flag? Glorious name.
Go back to your iPad.
What's happening?
You seem a little scared.
Finish it in one gulp. Aid.
Stop wiping your sweaty hands on your pants.
Do you feel better?
Better.
Look.
In the name of the Moon, I will destroy you.
Impressive technology.
Voice activated.
Do you want to try?
No, no, no.
Say it.
So shy.
Take.
Grab another can.
Too much beer.
I looked away for a second,
and you leave.
Add me on WeChat.
Let me know when the wedding is.
I'll contribute a little.
Fun guy.
Contribute...
Where is your grandfather?
Isn't he here to pick you up?
I'm going to give him a surprise.
Wait for me here.
I go to the bathroom,
then I will take you there.
Hey, stop.
Thief.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Are you OK?
Be careful with my bag.
Brilliant.
Your father can jump.
He's a police officer from the northeast,
Li Hongqi.
Listen to this name.
That thief is finished.
Hurry up.
I have to go.
I'm exhausted.
Run, run, run.
Do you believe Donnie Yen?
Get out of my way!
Are you filming me?
What is he up to?
Who is it?
Put down the phone.
What the devil...?
Kick his ass!
I...
Take his phone!
Why did you kick me?
- Kick his ass!  - Open the door!
My arm!
My head!
My hand!
Mister!
Lord,
let's talk about this.
Mister.
What is your name, sir?
To the airport police station.
Sure, sir.
Wait.
First find a bathroom.
Sure, sir.
Close that door.
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
Yes, I know her.
Understood.
Are you okay alone?
Yes of course.
What's happening?
Lord,
Please bring her home safely.
What has happened?
They said that
My mother-in-law was taken to the police station.
No fights.
Stop fighting.
what kind of scum
refuses to pay for a funeral?
I am the MC,
not your mother!
I don't deserve this!
- I don't deserve this!  - Stop fighting!
Come on, stop it!
Or I'll have to arrest you.
Arrest me?
He owes me money
and you arrest me?
We are from the same place, Zhao Deliang.
You're worse than a good old woman.
You are a disgrace to us Northeasterners.
Totally shameless!
Come on, hit me,
and we will call him
even.
Yes of course.
That will make up for the 200.
No fights, no fights!
He wants me to do it!
I will do that.
200 yuan of beating,
and you will still owe me 1,800.
What a terrifying woman.
Oh God!
They totally harassed me!
How unfair!
He started hitting her in the restaurant.
This is recorded by a spectator.
You have accepted an agreement
with one condition:
that you pay for the clothes.
Sounds fair.
His pants and shoes too...
You may have to pay for them.
Yes of course.
I'll also buy you a new pair of underwear.
Your mother-in-law is so temperamental.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Alright.
Liu...
Jiangshe?
Li Hongqi.
That's how it is.
Hongqi.
I remember it's a pretty old-fashioned name.
So...,
Did they reassign you here too?
You are...?
This is our Deputy Chief.
I used to be in the Jiangbei branch.
Sun Biao.
A pleasure.
He's a real hero, this guy.
A few famous battles in the old city
They were all directed by him.
I'm just an ordinary policeman.
But listen to me,
Hongqi.
Now times are different.
For future cases,
less action
and enforce the law in a civilized manner.
When you have problems,
use your wisdom
to solve them.
I have to go.
Us
I'll catch up later.
Later.
Hongqi.
That's right, Hongqi.
Who is that guy?
How pretentious.
- Let's get out of here.  - "In a civilized way."
It looks pretty bad.
Make me take you to the hospital
in case he tries to trick you.
Step aside, old man.
What nonsense
are you babbling?
You hit a man like that
and we can't say anything?
I was going in the wrong direction.
Boy, I can't take you anymore.
Get another taxi.
OK.
Child.
Son,
Don't be so tense with me.
You still don't know me,
but once you do,
You will see how different I am from Taozi's father.
We have been divorced for years.
He is a vulgar businessman.
I am a popular artist.
Watch where you're going!
No eyes!
And no sense of decency.
You know, in folk duet, funeral performance
It is considered a profession.
It used to be called "cultural heritage."
What is the new phrase?
"Transporting the soul."
Sincerely,
It is a very respectable job.
What are you looking at?
We are here.
Let's go.
You are a lucky girl.
You caught me between shifts,
otherwise you won't even be able to find another taxi.
Do I have to thank you for this?
You are welcome.
Give me 10 more yuan.
Do I look like 10 yuan to you?
Daring girl.
Hello, Erjie.
Who is it?
My son-in-law
Hello everyone.
65 for half a kilo.
Yesterday there were 60.
Now it's 65?
You didn't buy anything yesterday, right?
Lie.
I didn't even ask yesterday.
Give me a kilo, now.
Here they use coconut to make chicken stew.
Do you want some?
Yes of course.
I don't like those things.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Where are you driving?
I'm talking to you.
It's not like I'm going to sell you out or anything.
Where am I going...
To the bathroom.
It hit me on the chin.
No problem.
Good girl.
OK.
What are you doing?
They always do it on television,
trampling him.
Grab it!
Get her out of here.
You watch too much television,
Fool.
How are you?
My son-in-law
Hello.
(Call cancelled.)
(Xinxin: I'm at home.)
Here it is a specialty.
Drink it fresh.
Boss,
transferred payment.
It's okay, man.
Alright.
I'm fine.
What are you doing?
Well,
these things kept swinging
in your face.
Sit down.
No problem.
Let's start the meeting.
Let me introduce you,
my son-in-law
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, man.
Hello.
Qi Laosi.
He used to play the erhu in our company.
The erhu is no longer used at funerals.
Instead they use the suona horn.
That's your son over there,
Qi Laowu.
Father and son.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Zheng,
Zheng Sanpao.
Back at the company, Xiaoqin and I
They were performing partners.
When city officials visited,
They called us.
OK.
Officials then shut down the company.
Fuck off.
So insensitive.
You are jealous.
Was it true or not?
What truth?
Is that your sore?
What sensitive point?
You couldn't even get on stage.
Stop pointing at me!
I can point out all I want!
Do you want to fight?
Struggle? I don't mind.
You wouldn't dare.
I can beat you like this,
like a broken drum.
What do you think?
Laowu!
For.
He has a kitchen knife.
Enough already!
to you,
Get out!
Sit down!
Bastards.
You're lucky I'm here.
Back to the meeting.
We have to discuss
two important questions.
First,
welcoming my son-in-law.
Second,
I hereby announce
that the wedding preparation has officially begun.
Great.
I plan to give you
a wonderful
funeral on the lawn.
You don't have to worry about anything.
We will make sure everything is perfect,
and you will give Taozi
an amazing surprise.
You take care of the MC.
OK.
You are in charge of all the rehearsals.
Laowu makes the purchase.
to you,
go choose a dress,
and have your photos taken.
Listen,
essays
They are very important,
and you won't be able to handle it.
He doesn't know how to do tests.
I'm better than you.
Better than me?
You are not good.
Uncle.
- You can't afford... - Dude, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Taozi...
And Taozi?
He likes it simple.
Is that what he said?
What do you think?
I prefer it...
Simple.
That's how it is.
Do you see it?
He's doubting me.
You think I'm not doing it right
so I can't achieve it, right?
No, no, no.
I don't mean that.
I have decided
to take it all
two notches.
Great.
Anything else?
Then it's decided.
Look at me.
Hands in pockets.
Thumbs out.
Don't delay it.
Thumbs out of pockets.
Good.
Take two steps back.
Pretend to hold her hand and walk forward.
Now,
looks at the camera and smiles.
left hand,
left hand out,
right hand inside.
And clench your fists.
So that? This is not a fight.
Have your arm around Taozi.
We will put it in photoshop.
As if you were asking him for a dance.
Don't clench your fists.
Open, open.
Hello?
Who is it?
Li Hongqi, right?
This is Sun Biao,
from the police station.
Liu Xinxin?
Yes, I know her.
I met her on the plane.
It has disappeared.
As?
The taxi he took had an accident on the way.
The driver asked him to take another taxi,
and now she is missing.
Please wait until further notice.
Son.
Don't go anywhere for the next few days.
They didn't do it well.
Let's go back to filming.
-Li Hongqi.  - Listen to me this time.
Li Hongqi.
I'm going to the bathroom, then I'll take you.
Here, son.
look at me,
and smile.
That's how it is.
Have very happy thoughts.
Are you okay alone?
Yes of course.
Sir, please bring her home safely.
I'm a policeman.
Awesome.
Finish it in one gulp. Aid.
Stop wiping your sweaty hands on your pants.
Do you feel better?
Better.
Why do you fly alone?
Where is your family?
Busy making money.
They have a food stand.
My mother promised to visit my grandfather with me,
but he couldn't keep that promise.
I already promised my grandfather,
so I have to come, even if I'm alone.
But you,
you need to have someone with you on planes.
You are tired.
Continue,
take a nap
Sleep also helps.
Married, huh?
Done for life, huh?
It feels different.
Now he is relaxed.
When he smiles...
Aunt,
where are we with the wedding cars?
What wedding cars?
We need to have a fleet of cars for the wedding.
Ours is supposed to be Western style.
What do you think...
The band? The band.
Do you mean the erhu?
Not the erhu.
Western style.
Very good.
I'll figure it out, don't worry.
Look,
It's okay, auntie.
Leave it to me.
I know some people.
We could get a discount.
Leave it to me.
You didn't wash your hair.
He looks like he's being chased by a dog.
I left it a few days ago.
What is happening?
I can't tell you what's happening.
You know the rules, right?
We are both police officers.
Would you be able to stay seated?
Dahua,
come here
What's up, boss?
We have collected similar cases in nearby cities,
and now they suspect that
It is a transregional organized crime gang
that could be moving from one place to another.
It is currently suspected that the kidnapped children
could be transferred very soon.
Isn't this...
Isn't this what you just said at the meeting?
Did you really listen at the meeting?
I, I did it.
Get lost.
Do your job.
Incredible.
If I had sent her home, this wouldn't have happened.
I am partly responsible.
Can I help you?
Go home and wait.
You will do me a favor.
I'll wait here.
Whatever you want.
The illegal taxi that Xinxin got into had a fake license plate.
We lost it after this crossing.
I don't have enough manpower.
These are students we borrowed from the police academy.
If you want,
you can help here.
Aunt.
I'm with...
the leader of the band and everyone,
inviting them to eat.
Son,
what are you up to?
It took you a long time to collect.
I want to show you this photo.
What do you think?
Take,
look.
Aunt, you have to
turn the camera.
As?
The flip down button in the right corner.
OK.
What do you think of this one, son?
I'm going to photoshop Taozi in
Well...
Tell me if you like it or not.
It's a little...
Nothing happens.
Look at this one.
Wait.
This one's not even that...
I chose this one.
Then it's okay.
This is good.
Look at this one.
Aunt,
you choose them.
I trust you.
Old Camry, that's right.
The rear light seems broken.
Write down the time.
Good.
It's probably that one.
Broken right rear light.
It's this one.
We're already letting you join us.
Stay in the car.
Lord, sir,
let me out
Uncle,
That Camry below, is it yours?
It's blocking my car.
Move, will you?
Are you OK?
Dahua,
Stop it!
High!
Stop running!
Here!
Stop it!
Over there!
We are from the Haitang police station.
It's him.
What is your name?
Tell us what your name is.
Be careful with the attitude of law enforcement.
tell me,
to that girl yesterday,
where did you take her?
As?
What are you mumbling?
Whom?
No problem.
I see them.
You are hard to find.
What do you want?
Are you together?
He?
No.
I need to talk to him.
This has nothing to do with you.
Back, back!
Police, on duty.
Do you see it?
Debt collectors are so professional now.
I need one of these.
The bastard owes everyone money.
Let me warn you again.
We are the real police.
Lord,
I really don't have money.
Take the Camry downstairs.
Take a break, Mr. Police.
Back off, everyone!
Back!
You are attacking the police,
and I arrest you all!
Did you hit our Boss?
I'm sorry.
It's him!
What now, sir?
And now what?
Get it under control.
OK.
Nobody respects manners anymore.
Who are you?
Forward!
Dude, who the hell are you?
Whoever wins stays with me.
Dahua!
For.
I told you to stop!
I'm fine, sir.
I'm totally fine.
Your hands.
You can't act like that.
When faced with lawbreakers,
you
They need to show some spirit.
If not, who knows?
(Don't let him know I paid.)
The driver's name is Zhu Yong.
Not a word of truth from his mouth.
The blonde guy and his men are debt collectors
and they have nothing to do with the girl.
Your parents are coming here.
It's his grandfather.
I can't make him go away.
You don't have to be here either.
Go home.
When Taozi gets here,
we will take more.
Yeah.
Let's photoshop them together.
It's...
I'm back, auntie.
You're back, son. How did it go?
The band.
I have one.
How much?
Free.
Heavens.
You are the man! Free?
Sanpao,
contact them.
Rehearsal the day after tomorrow.
Understood.
Send me your WeChat details.
That's why they say,
wherever you are,
It's always easier if you know someone.
Don't tell me.
By the way,
The band leader has a small request.
This guy owes them money.
His name is Zhu Yong,
also from the northeast.
You know the community well.
See if you can help find it.
Son, it's him.
As?
Let go, let go.
Zhu Yong worked for me for a while.
He was stealing from me,
and I said goodbye to him.
Whatever I ended up doing,
I have no idea.
Uncle,
Think about it well.
Well,
Why don't you ask on the volleyball court?
Why are you looking for Yong?
He owes me money.
I really don't know him,
But I know his girlfriend pretty well.
Wait here a little.
I will introduce you.
I'm not his girlfriend.
We just... you know.
As?
Old man,
what do you ask for?
I was just asking.
Enough already.
A few days ago, one of his party colleagues said that
made some money somehow.
Why don't you ask him?
Assistant,
put another 20 for this one here.
Yong came to see me a while ago.
He said he was going to bounce.
But then he said no more,
and I started going to El Marinero every day.
That? What Sailor?
You don't even know The Sailor?
Great club.
Your boss,
Tang Hulu.
Tang Hulu?
From the northeast.
He was in prison, called Tang Jun, right?
Good.
We have this one.
I know that guy.
Thanks my friend.
This place seems a bit complicated.
Why don't you stay outside?
Misleading, really?
You're kidding me.
Pick up.
Tell him you're working.
OK.
- You don't even know how to lie... - Hello, Taozi.
And he's bossing me around.
Do you hear me?
Young.
As?
Where is Tang Hulu?
I don't know, I don't know.
I'm looking for Tang Hulu.
Whom?
Tang Hulu.
Are you deaf?
I'm looking for Tang Hulu!
Who are you?
Who am I?
Aunt Wang.
Don't you remember me?
Little brat.
From the Art Troupe family complex.
In 2013, when your father died, I organized the funeral.
Aunt Wang.
What do you want?
Man, you've gotten big.
A true large size.
You were so skinny as a child.
When I hugged you,
You always pissed on my hands.
Remember that time
when a group of children robbed you?
I have your money back.
you lamented
with the heart,
and I couldn't make you stop.
You had snot and tears all over your face,
and you were sniffling,
like "hulu, hulu."
That's how you got your nickname, Hulu.
Since then,
we started calling it Hulu.
Isn't it funny?
Hello? Say something.
Are you still there?
Are you okay, aunt?
I'm fine.
Don't lay a finger on me again!
Who do you think you are?
It's enough.
Back.
Nobody moves.
Let the Boss take care of it.
Yes.
The boss is the man.
You've got some training, huh?
No, no, no.
Make no mistake.
Do you see how long it is?
Longer than your life.
I'm here to ask some questions.
Enough already.
You're crazy!
Auntie, stop talking for now.
Be quiet.
Aunt Wang,
let me show you
what real kung fu is like.
Great.
He hasn't been right in the head since he was little.
Fantastic, Boss.
What are those applauses for?
Stop clapping.
Boss, Boss.
Take a look, Boss.
It's me, boss.
The boss is confused.
Come on,
Take it down!
Kick his ass!
Don't start.
Don't do it.
Son,
my legs are shaking.
No problem. Hold on to me.
ID.
Show me your ID.
I wanted to ask for someone,
and you had to start a fight.
Do you know Zhu Yong?
Not me, officer,
But I have something to report.
He's the security guard at Pier 3.
He often comes to bet...
No, play pool.
He has to inform you of something.
Forward.
Come on, sit down.
I would like
occasionally lets pass
illegal vehicles with false license plates,
in exchange for a little money.
Recently, there was a fresh produce van.
I let it go,
and he didn't pay any more attention.
But...,
last night...
The water was freezing.
that girl
must have died.
Xinxin!
Please!
Madam, madam,
please get up.
Lady, listen to me.
Please get up.
So that's what you've been working on
for a couple of days now.
Aunt, I...
Taozi's stupid father told me that
Your parents didn't raise you either.
Do you know them?
No.
All I know is that they left me in front of a post office.
I believe the girl will be found.
What do you think?
Yes,
definitely.
Aunt,
I actually want to have the wedding,
But I can't just walk away from this.
Can you give me a few more days?
Alright.
What's happening?
You sound apathetic.
I'm fine,
a little tired.
Bye, are you awake?
Something came up.
Hello,
Hongqi.
Hello, Chao.
Your joint research request has been approved.
Zhao and I will fly today.
Bye.
Hongqi,
The story you made up came true.
Tell it to me.
Zhao.
There's more in the back.
Lee,
what have you come for?
When you asked for leave, there were all kinds of stories.
Like what?
Like,
You are going to have a wedding with your mother-in-law.
Come on, Hongqi.
Introduce me to local colleagues.
Hello?
Li Hongqi,
We found Zhu Yong's handler.
Understood.
What, can't I ask you?
I see.
You said it, right?
What the devil...?
We don't have time.
Leave the bags. Let's go.
Where to?
Clubbing.
This woman
He is the one who distributes the jobs in El Marinero.
Every Saturday,
comes to this place.
We, the local police
runs the risk of being exposed.
You are more suitable
to investigate in disguise.
More suitable, huh?
Take.
Look here.
His name is Zhao Bingbing,
and has two accomplices.
one of them
He is a tall and big guy.
The other one has a beard.
Both recognizable
and easy to find.
Lee,
How are we supposed to find them?
There are no human beings here, everything is mammals.
I don't see any goal here either.
And Chao?
He has sharp eyes.
Is there something there, Chao?
Look at that chicken.
Chicken? where?
Isn't it a chicken?
Bye,
that's not a chicken.
What chicken?
Look at it.
Wait.
There is a tall and big tiger
heading to the center of the stage.
OK.
I'll go confirm it.
Get lost.
Excuse me.
Confirmed.
It's her.
I'm on it.
New things.
That's what they drink on the West Coast.
It keeps you partying all night.
Really?
The things you brought last time
it didn't work at all,
It just gave me the races.
Then don't take any.
Happiness pills?
It keeps you happy.
Who are you?
Women.
Beard.
Stupid big guy.
It's you three.
Wrong.
Not the three of us.
The police.
Get down!
square face,
Catch him!
Loser.
Li.
Are you OK?
Now, the most modern,
and the wildest moment
that you were all waiting for.
Let the party begin!
I'm done, I'm done.
You are so brutal!
Do you know why they arrest you?
The pills.
Think before you speak.
Where is the child?
What child?
Don't know.
You don't know, huh?
Do you know what happens if you don't work with us?
Look,
let me tell you something.
Whoever speaks first gets the best deal.
If they speak first,
We will no longer be interested in what you have to say.
Forget it.
Let's talk to someone else.
What child?
So there was more than one child.
It was really the first time for us.
We just wanted money for pills.
It was hard enough getting five kids together,
and the day before yesterday, we took them to Pier 3.
But there was a boy who was a pain in the ass.
Children,
we are here.
Careful.
Damn it, Bing!
They escape!
Runs!
The ocean.
Jump.
Do you know how deep it is?
You will drown.
Fuck off!
Come back here!
He fell inside.
We searched the coast for hours,
and I thought he had died.
Ma'am, I need to call the police.
Can you make the call for me?
Lady.
I need to call the police. Call the police for me.
I need to use your phone.
Make the call for me.
I have to call the police.
OK.
Why don't you get in the car first?
We'll take you to the police station.
I'm not going to get in the car.
Make the call for me.
I'm going to call the police.
I get it, I get it.
Get in the car first.
I'm not going to get in the car. I'm going to call the police.
Let me use your phone.
I get it, I get it.
Don't be angry.
Mrs. Qin,
are you here already?
A brat fell into the sea.
We are looking for her.
Today we teach you two methods.
The first.
Here, be a father.
Come.
Block parent's view,
and then,
others have
talk to the boy.
What nonsense.
I don't even hear what he says.
I don't hear him either.
Can you manage?
Just kidnapping children, right?
All it takes is strength.
Do you have it?
OK.
Now, the Second Group.
My name is Zhou.
I'm from the countryside.
I got into online gaming.
I lost all the money,
and my wife left me.
Stay calm.
Now that you are in this place,
you will surely earn money.
What are you laughing at?
Haven't you made the money?
TRUE?
Mrs. Qin and her husband
They are manipulators of Zhao Bingbing and his gang.
They were brainwashed
a bunch of unemployed bums to provide the source of supply.
According to Zhao Bingbing, Qin has many customers,
the most ingenious of which is the fishmonger.
But they haven't met any of the clients,
and they only know that the children are sent abroad.
Do we have the location of this Mrs. Qin?
Zhao Bingbing once followed them secretly.
to an abandoned neighborhood under the Southern Highway.
(I will go.)
(You ask for reinforcements.)
You, stranger,
a braggart
Let me put it this way.
my movements
They are as good as yours.
Boss Biao! Boss Biao!
Boss Biao!
Stay still! Police!
Raise your hands.
Now!
Don't move,
or I shoot!
Come on.
Raise your hand.
Forward!
Xiaohua.
Boss Biao, it's me.
Li Hongqi.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
The woman ran away.
Mrs. Qin?
Raise your hands.
Kneel down and lie face down on the floor!
Now!
Don't move,
or I will shoot you.
I waited and waited, and you never came.
I thought it was delivery day.
Where are my adorable fish?
Dahua.
Stay strong.
You are a man,
And it's a small wound, right?
Dahua,
stay strong!
They found thirteen children in that house,
but not Liu Xinxin.
Before Dahua fainted, he was murmuring that
The guy who hit him spoke Cantonese.
He could be Qin's controller.
Tang Hulu has new information.
A group of out-of-town human traffickers
They are planning a transaction tonight.
They are dealing with Madam Qin.
Let's see if he can get some information out of them.
No drinking tonight. We have business.
What type of business?
Tell me.
Maybe I can help.
But Madam Qin has no other children in her hands,
and he is not selling to his usual handler, El Pescadero.
Something is wrong.
There is no time to guess.
They are very cautious,
and keep locations separate.
We have to separate.
OK.
Madam,
we are here.
OK.
I told you to sell me your shares.
That fishmonger is not good.
Check the merchandise.
OK.
This.
This one is pretty too.
Empty.
bitch,
Are you kidding me?
Take the one from the car.
Chief Biao,
this is a fake location.
No Mrs. Qin,
no child,
and no Cantonese.
We don't have the actual location.
He must be escaping.
Surveillance has been established at all exits of the city and key areas.
Chief Biao,
look at this.
We just received a file on Madam Qin.
I'm sending it to you.
Send it.
Madam Qin, called Qin Yerong,
They came here illegally as smugglers.
A man was found,
she had a son with him,
and was involved in many illegal businesses.
When his daughter, Xiaohua, was five years old,
died in an accident.
After that, Qin became mentally unstable.
And this Xiaohua
He looked like Xinxin.
(Xiaohua.)
(It looks like her, but it's not her).
Xiaohua.
We also receive other essential information.
Madam Qin has set up a front as a fruit seller.
at the Old Street Market.
Old Street Market?
Understood.
We are closer.
We'll go take a look.
Winning tile.
Today you are holding on a lot,
your mouths looser than fat men's pants.
How am I supposed to play with you?
Simply endless.
You just have bad luck.
I'm not going to play anymore.
Bad luck.
Help me.
Don't worry.
No problem.
Hello, son.
I saw the girl you're looking for.
That woman is trying to escape,
and I'm hot on his heels
at Bay Harbor Market.
Understood.
Now he is in the Fisherman's Village.
I know this place well.
It can't go fast.
Come here quickly.
Damn.
I'm two kilometers away.
He is about to leave the town.
The railway has just passed.
They go towards the old stone bridge,
past which there is a pier.
Understood, aunt.
Be very careful.
Don't worry. I'm on it.
Aunt.
Aunt, are you okay?
Son,
I lost them.
Damn!
Aunt.
I caught them, auntie.
I caught them.
She looks like a woman.
Bye,
I'll go confirm it.
If she flees, intercept her.
Clear. Be careful.
Bye.
Are you OK?
Damn you.
I told you.
My moves are just as good.
Take care of Chao for me.
Li Hongqi,
be careful.
Did you hear something?
Sit down, sit down.
You've arrived just in time.
Yangzhou fried rice.
You are lucky.
little girl,
how old are you?
No manners.
(Take me abroad.)
There is no rush.
Eat first.
It's good?
I haven't done anything.
Don't let her die.
I need it to make money,
Do you understand?
Understood.
The police.
Who do you have on this island?
Come on, come on.
Sorry, officer.
There is nothing here.
Just a fishing island.
What do you want?
Out!
Back up, police.
Do you understand, cop?
I said go!
Back!
Fresh out of the wok.
Do you want to try?
Did you wipe out my colleague?
So you don't want it?
I'll have it myself.
Did you hit him?
It was in my way.
I hereby officially notify you
to return with me to the police station to investigate it.
Are you resisting arrest?
Then I have to arrest you.
You like lying on the floor, huh?
So lie down.
Ouch, that hurts.
So stop fighting.
Work with me.
You will earn more than now.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I said,
I promise you.
great wealth.
And I lost a tooth.
Don't make promises
that you can't keep.
Let go of me, bitch.
Don't be afraid.
No problem.
Li Hongqi.
Xinxin,
In the name of the Moon, I will destroy you.
As?
Say it!
Go home.
I want to go home.
Team One in position.
Team Two in position too.
Ambulance in position, confirming casualties and injuries.
Do you see it? I said Li would be fine.
It's okay, it's okay.
In the name of the Moon, I will destroy you.
You're no better on the boat.
It turns out that,
You can't trust my mother-in-law.
Check the calendar, but not the time.
A rainy typhoon
ruined the entire wedding venue.
So the wedding on the lawn
had to be moved to the terrace.
Two levels up, in fact.
Fortunately, Taozi was happy,
my mother-in-law was happy,
and I was happy.
Hello?
Hello, Chief Biao.
They left on a boat.
I couldn't follow it.
Ask her where they are taking her.
tell us,
where is the girl?